{
    "subject": "Amrita_Singh",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Saif_Ali_Khan",
    "human_readable": "Amrita Singh is married to Saif Ali Khan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9871492981910706,
            "question": "Is there a marriage between Amrita Singh and Saif Ali Khan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9384257197380066,
            "question": "To whom is Amrita Singh married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9303800463676453,
            "question": "Who is Amrita Singh married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9210398197174072,
            "question": "Are Amrita Singh and Saif Ali Khan in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9145025014877319,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the relationship between Amrita Singh and Saif Ali Khan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9020057916641235,
            "question": "Is Saif Ali Khan married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9018919467926025,
            "question": "Who is Saif Ali Khan married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7572128176689148,
            "question": "What is the name of Amrita Singh's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7366402745246887,
            "question": "What is the name of Saif Ali Khan's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19892603158950806,
            "question": "Who are the individuals involved in this marriage?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Amrita Singh is married to Saif Ali Khan.",
            "html": "yago_30247_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Saif Ali Khan's wife?",
            "html": "yago_30247_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Amrita Singh's husband?",
            "html": "yago_30247_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Saif Ali Khan married to?",
            "html": "yago_30247_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30247_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30247_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30247_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30247_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30247_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30247_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30247_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30247_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30247_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30247_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents clearly state that Saif Ali Khan was previously married to Amrita Singh, and they divorced in 2004. There is no information suggesting that they are currently married. Therefore, the statement \"Amrita Singh is married to Saif Ali Khan\" is incorrect based on the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several passages state they are divorced.",
            "category": 0
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Amrita Singh divorced Saif Ali Khan in 2004, and they are no longer married.",
            "category": 0
        }
    }
}